A Guide to the Virginia Dietetic Association Collection
Claude Moore Health Sciences Library
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Teller's Committee, 1986-1987, AD(2) (Box-folder 020:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Nominating Committee, 1986-1987, TD(5) (Box-folder 020:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Continuing Education, 1986-1987, TD(13) (Box-folder 020:015)
  Reports, Continuing Education Program Evaluation Agreement, California Dietetic Association Guideline for Continuing Education
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Elizabeth Lounds Memorial Lecture, 1986-1987, TD(2) (Box-folder 020:016)
  Lecture Announcement
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Public Relations, 1986-1987, TD(4), AD(1) (Box-folder 020:017)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: State Media Representatives, 1986-1987, TD(5) (Box-folder 020:018)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Share Our Pride Campaign, 1986-1987, TD(15), Pamphlet(1), Newsletter Articles(2) (Box-folder 020:019)
  Membership Listing, Reports, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Clinical Dietetics and Research, 1986-1987, TD(3) (Box-folder 020:020)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Executive Board, 1986-1987, TD(12) (Box-folder 021:001)
  Membership Listing
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Executive Board Meeting Agenda, 1986-1987, TD(18), AD(1) (Box-folder 021:002)
  Reports, Letters, Map
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Calendar of Activities, 1986-1987, TD(6) (Box-folder 021:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: General Correspondence, 1986-1987, TD(52), AD(2) (Box-folder 021:004)
  Letters, Recipes, Book Order Form, Map, W-9 Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Correspondence from ADA, 1986-1987, TD(25), Newspaper Articles(8) (Box-folder 021:005)
  Poster Session Request Form, Medalion Award Nomination Forms, Memoranda, Request for Proposal on "Nutrition Education for the Public"
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Correspondence with District Presidents, 1986-1987, TD(44), Pamphlet(2), Flyer(1) (Box-folder 021:006)
  Reports, Letters, Workshop on Foodservice Management Pamphlet, Diabetes Education Update, Meeting Reports, Disbursement Request Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Minutes, 1986-1987, TD(11) (Box-folder 021:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Treasurer, 1986-1987, TD(134), AD(19) (Box-folder 021:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Affiliate Liability Insurance, 1986-1987, TD(14) (Box-folder 021:009)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Bylaws, 1986-1987, TD(26) (Box-folder 021:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Standing Rules, 1986-1987, TD(31) (Box-folder 021:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Blue Ridge Dietetic Association, 1986-1987, TD(4) (Box-folder 021:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association, 1986-1987, TD(20), AD(1), Newsletters(3), Pamphlets(2), Flyers(5) (Box-folder 021:013)
  Reports, Letters, Meeting Announcements
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Richmond Dietetic Association, 1986-1987, TD(10), Newsletters(4), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 021:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Southwest Dietetic Association, 1986-1987, TD(2), Newsletters(2) (Box-folder 021:015())
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Tidewater Dietetic Association, 1986-1987, TD(9) (Box-folder 021:016)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: National Nutrition Month, 1986-1987, TD(41) (Box-folder 022:001)
  Reports, Letters, National Nutrition Month Information Kit
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Career Guidance, 1986-1987, TD(6) (Box-folder 022:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Legislation, 1986-1987, TD(31), Flyer(1), pamphlet(1), Newsletters(2) (Box-folder 022:003)
  Reports, House Bill No. 1474, Fact Sheets, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Licensure, 1986-1987, TD(68) (Box-folder 022:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Nutrition PAC, 1986-1987, TD(1), Pamphlets(2), Booklet(1) (Box-folder 022:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Infant Mortality Task Force, 1986-1987, TD(32), Journal Articles(5), Pamphlets(1) (Box-folder 022:006)
  Reports, Memoranda,
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: NSPS, 1986-1987, TD(2), AD(1) (Box-folder 022:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Council on State Legislation, 1986-1987, TD(6), AD(2), pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 022:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Perinatal Services Advisory Board, 1986-1987, TD(13) (Box-folder 022:009)
  Letters, CV(Jean Dimartino)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia Association of Allied Health Professions (VAAHP), 1986-1987, TD(8) (Box-folder 022:010)
  Memoranda, Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia Health Council, 1986-1987, TD(4), Newsletters(2) (Box-folder 022:011)
  Letters, Minute, Momorandum
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Consulting Nutritionists in the Chesapeake Bay Area, 1986-1987, TD(6), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 022:012)
  Reports, Letters, Minute
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Committee on Attendance at VDA Meetings, 1986-1987, TD(9) (Box-folder 022:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: VDA Member List, 1986-1987, TD (Box-folder 022:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Strategic Plan Report, 1987-1988, TD(16), Booklet(1) (Box-folder 023:001)
  Transparency Masters for Presentation
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Bylaws, 1987-1988, TD(14) (Box-folder 023:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Standing Rules, 1987-1988, TD(20) (Box-folder 023:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Treasurer, 1987-1988, TD(132) (Box-folder 023:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Finance Committee, 1987-1988, TD(7), AD(8) (Box-folder 023:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: NDVDA, 1987-1988, TD(7), Newsletters(2) (Box-folder 023:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Richmond Dietetic Association, 1987-1988, TD(8) (Box-folder 023:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Southwest Dietetic Association, 1987-1988, Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 023:008)
  Fight Against Nutrition Fraud
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Tidewater Dietetic Association, 1987-1988, TD(5) (Box-folder 023:009)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Council on Practice, 1987-1988, TD(24) (Box-folder 023:010)
  Reports, Memorandum, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Consultation and Private Practice, 1987-1988, TD(9) (Box-folder 023:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Community Division, 1987-1988, TD(8), AD(5) (Box-folder 023:012)
  Reports, Letters, Flyer, List of VDA Perinatal Nutritionists
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Division of Education and Research, 1987-1988, TD(1) (Box-folder 023:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Clinical Dietetics, 1987-1988, TD(2) (Box-folder 023:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Management Division, 1987-1988, TD(4) (Box-folder 023:015)
  Report, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Delegate's Reports, 1987-1988, TD(32) (Box-folder 023:016)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA Foundation, 1987-1988, TD(39), AD(2), Newsletter(1), Receipt(1) (Box-folder 023:017)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Long Range Plan, 1987-1988, TD(11) (Box-folder 023:018)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Awards and Scholarship, 1987-1988, TD(12) (Box-folder 023:019)
  Letters, Guidelines, Nomination Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Nominating Committee, 1987-1988, TD(2), AD(1) (Box-folder 023:020)
  Letters, Memorandum
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Continuing Education, 1987-1988, TD(17) (Box-folder 023:021)
  Program Evaluation Forms, Letters, Report
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: State Media Representatives, 1987-1988, TD(27) (Box-folder 023:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Public Relations, 1987-1988, TD(4) (Box-folder 023:023)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Licensure, 1987-1988, TD(87) (Box-folder 023:024)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Legislation, 1987-1988, TD(48), AD(5), Newsletters(8), Flyer(2), Pamphlets(5) (Box-folder 023:025)
  Reports, Letters, Symposium Content, Memorandum, Photocopy of Cogressional Report Card
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Elizabeth Lounds Lecture, 1987-1988, TD(6) (Box-folder 023:026)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Executive Board, 1987-1988, TD(9) (Box-folder 024:001)
  Membership list
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Board Meetings, 1987-1988, TD(23) (Box-folder 024:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Calendar of 1988, 1987-1988, TD(3) (Box-folder 024:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA Correspondence, 1987-1988, TD(80), Newsletters(2), Booklet(1) (Box-folder 024:004)
  Letters, 1986 Census Report, Survey Forms, Membership Listing, 50 Year Member List, Memoranda
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: General Correspondence, 1987-1988, TD(51), Flyer(1) (Box-folder 024:005)
  Letters, Poster Session Request Form, Outstanding Dietitiam Award Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia Health Council, 1987-1988, TD(8) (Box-folder 024:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia Association of Allied Health Professions (VAAHP), 1987-1988, TD(6) (Box-folder 024:007)
  Memoranda
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: NSPS, 1987-1988, TD(2) (Box-folder 024:008)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Career Guidance, 1987-1988, TD(3) (Box-folder 024:009)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: VDA Lines, 1987-1988, TD(2) (Box-folder 024:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Leading Edge Outreach Conference, 1987-1988, TD(13), AD(2) (Box-folder 024:011)
  Report, Letters, Memoranda
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Perinatal Board, 1987-1988, TD(15), Newsletters(2), Journal(1), Journal Articles(4), Pamphlets(1), Flyer(2), Newspaper Article(1) (Box-folder 024:012)
  Report, Letters, Memoranda, Health Careers Reference Manual with Advertising Contract Forms, Leading Edge Outreach Conference Package, Feedback Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Dietetic Technicians, 1987-1988, TD(10) (Box-folder 024:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Historian, 1987-1988, TD(3) (Box-folder 024:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Licensure, 1988-1989, TD(265), Pamphlet(1) (Box-folder 025:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA, 1988-1989, TD(21), Pamphlets(1), Newsletters(6) (Box-folder 025:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: NCND Fund Raising, 1988-1989, TD(29), AD(1), Pamphlets(3), Newsletters(5) (Box-folder 025:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia Association of Allied Health Professions, 1988-1989, TD(39), Newsletters(3), Manual(1) (Box-folder 025:004)
  Letters, Reports, Memoranda, Health Careers Reference Manual
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Membership List, 1988-1989, TD(58) (Box-folder 025:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Executive Board, 1988-1989, TD(74), AD(3), Pamphlets(2) (Box-folder 025:006)
  Reports, Letters, Survey Forms, Maps, Newsletter Article
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Long-Range Plan, 1988-1989, TD(21) (Box-folder 025:007)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Minutes, 1988-1989, TD(20) (Box-folder 025:008)
  Minutes, Contract Form for Administrative Services, Standing Rules
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Finance, 1988-1989, TD(85), AD(10) (Box-folder 025:009)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Delegates, 1988-1989, TD(61) (Box-folder 026:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Programs, 1988-1989, TD(39), Pamphlets(4), Flyer(1) (Box-folder 026:002)
  Reports, Letter, Lecture Evaluation Forms, Photocopy of a Check
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Bylaws, 1988-1989, TD(71), AD(1) (Box-folder 026:003)
  Bylaws and Amendments, Standing Rules, Reports, Letter
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: VDA Lines, 1988-1989, TD(9), AD(2) (Box-folder 026:004)
  Contract Agreement Form, Repports, Letters, Memo
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Awards, 1988-1989, TD(14) (Box-folder 026:005)
  Reports, Memo, Scholarship Application Form, Nomination Form, Guidelines
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Nominating Committee, 1988-1989, TD(6) (Box-folder 026:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Public Relations, 1988-1989, TD(23) (Box-folder 026:007)
  Reports, Letters, Reading List
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: State Media Representative, 1988-1989, TD(24) (Box-folder 026:008)
  Reports, Performance Form, Letter, Evaluation Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Council on Practice, 1988-1989, TD(23), Pamphlet(3) (Box-folder 026:009)
  Reports, Letters, Guidelines, Memorandum
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Clinical Dietetics, 1988-1989, TD(1) (Box-folder 026:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Community Dietetics, 1988-1989, TD(9), AD(3) (Box-folder 026:011)
  Reports, Memoranda, VDA Perinatal Nutritionists List
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Consultation and Private Practice, 1988-1989, TD(4) (Box-folder 026:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Education and Research, 1988-1989, TD(1) (Box-folder 026:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Management Practice Group, 1988-1989, TD(2) (Box-folder 026:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Career Guidance, 1988-1989, TD(2) (Box-folder 026:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: NSPS, 1988-1989, TD(5), Pamphlets(2) (Box-folder 026:016)
  Letters, Report
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Affirmative Action, 1988-1989, TD(17) (Box-folder 026:017)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Dietetic Technicians Registered(DTR), 1988-1989, TD(8), Newsletter(1) (Box-folder 026:018)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Tidewater Dietetic Association, 1988-1989, TD(5) (Box-folder 026:019)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Blue Ridge Dietetic Association, 1988-1989, TD(2) (Box-folder 026:020)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association, 1988-1989, TD(5), Newsletters(2) (Box-folder 026:021)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Richmond Dietetic Association, 1988-1989, TD(30) (Box-folder 026:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Southwest Dietetic Association, 1988-1989, TD(4) (Box-folder 026:023)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Legislation, 1988-1989, TD(92), Newsletters(9), Pamphlets(5), AD(1), Flyer(1), Newspaper Articles(1) (Box-folder 026:024)
  Reports, Photocopy of Congressional Report Card, Letters, House Joint Resolutions, Survey Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Continuing Education, 1988-1989, TD(11) (Box-folder 026:025)
  Hous Log, Evaluation Forms, Reports
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Executive Board, 1989-1990, TD(10) (Box-folder 027:001)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Calendar of Events, 1989-1990, TD(3) (Box-folder 027:002)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Agenda, 1989-1990, TD(9) (Box-folder 027:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Minutes, 1989-1990, TD(14) (Box-folder 027:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Executive Board Orientation, 1989-1990, TD(2), AD(1) (Box-folder 027:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Treasurer's Reports, 1989-1990, TD(91) (Box-folder 027:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Bylaws, 1989-1990, TD(19) (Box-folder 027:007)
  Letters, Bylaws
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: House of Delegates, 1989-1990, TD(92), AD(2), Newsletters(2) (Box-folder 027:008)
  Reports, Letters, Memorandum, Meeting Procedures, Guidelines, Suggestion Form, Bylaws
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Long Range Planning, 1989-1990, TD(25) (Box-folder 027:009)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Council on Practice, 1989-1990, TD(8) (Box-folder 027:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Division of Community, 1989-1990, TD(2), AD(2) (Box-folder 027:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Division of Consultation and Private Practice, 1989-1990, TD(3) (Box-folder 027:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Management Division, 1989-1990, TD(2) (Box-folder 027:013)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Council Division, 1989-1990, TD(1) (Box-folder 027:014)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Education and Research, 1989-1990, TD(6) (Box-folder 027:015)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Continuing Education, 1989-1990, TD(9) (Box-folder 027:016)
  Reports of Continuing Education Hours
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: National Nutrition Month, 1989-1990, TD(23), Flyer(1) (Box-folder 027:017)
  Reports, Contest Entry Form and Score Card, Virginia School Food Service Association Membership Listing, Memorandum of Agreement, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Legislation, 1989-1990, TD(65), AD(2), Photocopies of Newspaper(1), Newsletters(7), Envelope(1) (Box-folder 027:018)
  Reports, Letters, Flyer, Federal Registers, Virginia Board of Health Professions Membership Roster
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: ADA Foundation, 1989-1990, TD(6) (Box-folder 027:019)
  Reports, Letters, Annuual Fund Campaign Undate
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Licensure, 1989-1990, TD(7) (Box-folder 027:020)
  Reports, Licensing Guidebook Order Form
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Public Relations, 1989-1990, TD(14) (Box-folder 027:021)
  Reports, Media Handbook Outline
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Scholarships and Awards, 1989-1990, TD(10), Newsletters(3) (Box-folder 027:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Fall Meeting, 1989-1990, TD(8) (Box-folder 027:023)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Spring Meeting, 1989-1990, TD(9), Pamphlets(4) (Box-folder 027:024)
  Reports, VDA 60th Anniversary Program Schedule, Annual Meeting and Elizabeth Loubds Lecture Pamphlet, Award Luncheon Pamphlet
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Blue Ridge Dietetic Associaion, 1989-1990, TD(1), Newsletters(1) (Box-folder 027:025)
  Reports, Professional Development Award Application Form, Membership List
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Northern District Virginia Dietetic Association, 1989-1990, TD(5) (Box-folder 027:026)
  Reports, Membership List
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Richmond Dietetic Association, 1989-1990, Newsletters(8) (Box-folder 027:027)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Southwest Dietetic Association, 1989-1990, TD(8) (Box-folder 027:028)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Tidewater Dietetic Association, 1989-1990, TD(16) (Box-folder 027:029)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Nutrition Services Payment Systems(NSPS), 1989-1990, TD(42), Newsletters(1), Pamphlets(1) (Box-folder 027:030)
  Reports, Superbill Order Form, Memorandum, Membership List, List of Workshop Participants
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Administrative Services, 1989-1990, TD(33), AD(31) (Box-folder 028:001)
  Letters, Reports, CVs, Interview Documents, Contract, Patient Census
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Correspondences, 1989-1990, TD(60), AD(1) (Box-folder 028:002)
  Letters, ADA Membership Database, Poster Session Request Form, Outstanding Dietitian Award Application Form, Registration Forms, ADA Affiliates Logos, Reports, Memorandum, Nominee Suggestion Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Nominating Committee, 1989-1990, TD(10) (Box-folder 028:003)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: VDA Lines, 1989-1990, TD(3), Newsletters(2) (Box-folder 028:004)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Distinguished Dietitian Award, 1989-1990, TD(1), AD(1) (Box-folder 028:005)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Dietetic Technitians, 1989-1990, TD(1) (Box-folder 028:006)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: State Media Representative, 1989-1990, TD(7) (Box-folder 028:007)
  Report, Letter, Evaluation
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Exhibits, 1989-1990, TD(6) (Box-folder 028:008)
  Report, Letter, Mailing List
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Affirmative Action, 1989-1990, TD(7) (Box-folder 028:009)
  Report, Minority Recruitment and Retention Form, Minority Recruitment and Retention Plan
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Perinatal Services Advisory Board(PSAB), 1989-1990, TD(2) (Box-folder 028:010)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia School Food Service Association, 1989-1990, TD(1) (Box-folder 028:011)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia Health Council, 1989-1990, TD(9) (Box-folder 028:012)
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Virginia Association of Allied Health Professions, 1989-1990, TD(1) (Box-folder 028:013)
  Newsletter
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: State Talk, 1989-1990, TD(9), Newsletters(3) (Box-folder 028:014)
  Order Form, Reports, World Summit For Children
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: Recruitment and Retention for the Profession, 1989-1990, TD(11) (Box-folder 028:015)
  Letter, Reports, Evaluation Form, Mailing List
- Virginia Dietetic Association President's File: CDR Report, 1989-1990, TD(3) (Box-folder 028:016)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Executive Board, 1991-1992, TD(1) (Box-folder 028:017)
  Executive Board Membership
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Agenda, 1991-1992, TD(8) (Box-folder 028:018)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Minutes, 1991-1992, TD(26) (Box-folder 028:019)
  Meeting Minuets, Letters
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Bylaws, 1991-1992, TD(13) (Box-folder 028:020)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Treasurer's Reports, 1991-1992, TD(33) (Box-folder 028:021)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Finance Committee, 1991-1992, TD(10), AD(14) (Box-folder 028:022)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Divisions of Practice, 1991-1992, TD(17) (Box-folder 028:023)
  Reports, Evaluation Forms
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: President-Elect Reports, 1991-1992, TD(5) (Box-folder 028:024)
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Delegates Reports, 1991-1992, TD(28), Newsletters(2), Flyer(1) (Box-folder 028:025)
  Reports, Membership Listing, CV
- Virginia Dietetic Association: President's File: Council on Practice, 1991-1992, TD(8) (Box-folder 028:026)
  Letter, Poster Registration Form, Grant Application Form, Grant Application Guide, Report